<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Legacy Idrc Ocad</title>
	<atom:link href="https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:42:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/calogo.png</url>
	<title>Legacy Idrc Ocad</title>
	<link>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>North Korea to launch artificial satellite for spying</title>
		<link>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/north-korea-to-launch-artificial-satellite-for-spying/</link>
					<comments>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/north-korea-to-launch-artificial-satellite-for-spying/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the spy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/?p=22</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[North Korea will launch a military satellite to monitor the military activities of the US and its allies. It will be launched for spying next June. State-owned media reported this Tuesday, quoting...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>North Korea will launch a military satellite to monitor the military activities of the US and its allies. It will be launched for spying next June. State-owned media reported this Tuesday, quoting a senior defense official of the country.</p>



<p>Japan said on Monday that it has learned that Pyongyang may launch an artificial satellite this week.</p>



<p>The country&#8217;s state-run Korean Central News Agency quoted Ri Pyong-chol, vice chairman of the Central Military Commission of North Korea&#8217;s ruling party, as saying that the &#8216;Military Reconnaissance Satellite Number One&#8217; will be launched in June.</p>



<p>Earlier on April 13, North Korea tested a new intercontinental ballistic missile. According to the country&#8217;s government, it is a &#8216;solid fuel&#8217; missile. The name is &#8216;Hwasong-18&#8217;.</p>



<p>The missile is said to be the &#8216;most powerful&#8217; in North Korea&#8217;s arsenal. According to the state-owned media KCNA, Hwasong-18 can be launched relatively quickly as a solid fuel missile. These missiles are difficult to detect and counter.</p>



<p>North Korean leader Kim Jong-un said at the time that the successful test of the intercontinental ballistic missile Hwasong-18 would increase the fear and anxiety of rival countries.</p>



<p>Last March, a major joint military exercise &#8216;Freedom Shield 23&#8217; was held between South Korea and the United States. It is the largest US-South Korea joint military exercise in five years. North Korea opposes this exercise. Before and after the exercise, the country showed its strength by firing one missile after another.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/north-korea-to-launch-artificial-satellite-for-spying/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sanitary pads: Women came to the attention of the world from the shacks</title>
		<link>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/sanitary-pads-women-came-to-the-attention-of-the-world-from-the-shacks/</link>
					<comments>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/sanitary-pads-women-came-to-the-attention-of-the-world-from-the-shacks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Africa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Awareness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reproductive health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women&#039;s Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/?p=19</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tamara Magwashu&#8217;s family was in financial trouble. The family could not afford to buy him sanitary napkins during his schooling. Tamara was teased by schoolmates during her period. Tamara grew up in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Tamara Magwashu&#8217;s family was in financial trouble. The family could not afford to buy him sanitary napkins during his schooling. Tamara was teased by schoolmates during her period.</p>



<p>Tamara grew up in a poor suburb of South Africa&#8217;s Eastern Cape Province. Age now 27 years. His mother is a &#8216;single mother.&#8217; As a child, she saw her mother using old clothes during menstruation.</p>



<p>Tamara took at least a week off from school during menstruation. He had to learn to use clothes like his mother, even if it was uncomfortable. Tamara is now using that difficult childhood experience. She said, &#8216;I didn&#8217;t want the situation I went through during my period to be with anyone else.&#8217; Tamara plans to build an organization to alleviate the suffering of the poor during menstruation. And now he distributed sanitary pads to hundreds of schools in the Eastern Cape from that institution.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">From the shack to the world</h2>



<p>Tamara Magwashu is starting to get recognition for this work. This year, he has been nominated in the list of 30 entrepreneurs and social changemakers under the age of 30 (Thirty Under Thirty) of the American magazine &#8216;Forbes&#8217;. This list is made with young entrepreneurs from different countries of the world.</p>



<p>Tamara tells the story of her life in Duncan Village, East London. He said, he spent his whole life in a shack. There were no windows in this room. There was no water line.</p>



<p>After leaving school he decided to work part-time. The idea was to support the family from the earnings of this job. Also thought that during menstruation she could spend money on sanitary pads.</p>



<p>Tamara also said, &#8216;Aside from studying, I started working. So that I can buy sanitary pads from my earnings. It is very uncomfortable to use cloth during menstruation.&#8217;</p>



<p>Tamara also said that there was very little knowledge about menstruation at that time. Because of this, it was very difficult to understand why she was having menstrual pain as a teenager. Tamara was not the only one who went through such a situation. Countless girls and women have gone through this situation and are still going through it.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/sanitary-pads-women-came-to-the-attention-of-the-world-from-the-shacks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Most students fail in Texas, USA</title>
		<link>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/most-students-fail-in-texas-usa/</link>
					<comments>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/most-students-fail-in-texas-usa/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[America]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Everything is ready for the graduation party. The festival will be held after the announcement of the results. But it didn&#8217;t happen anymore. The festival was cancelled. Because most of the students...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Everything is ready for the graduation party. The festival will be held after the announcement of the results. But it didn&#8217;t happen anymore. The festival was cancelled. Because most of the students failed. This happened in Texas, America.</p>



<p>According to the New York Post, there are 33 students in a diploma course at Marlin High School in Texas. 28 failed in the end of course examination, only 5 passed. As most of the students failed, the graduation ceremony was stopped in that high school in the United States. Not only failed, the attendance rate of these 28 students is also very low.</p>



<p>According to a CNN report, the date of the re-organization of the graduation ceremony has been announced at the high school in Texas. Merlin High School said in a Facebook post that the date of the graduation ceremony will be announced in June. However, before this, the attendance and academic results of the failed students should be improved.</p>



<p>The initiative is part of a larger effort by Marlin Independent School District to meet student success and academic expectations, the school said. They also said that the district has announced to provide all necessary facilities and support to the students. And as part of fulfilling this promise, the graduation program has been given a new date.</p>



<p>&#8220;We remain steadfast in our commitment to student success,&#8221; the school&#8217;s principal, Daryl Henson, said in a statement. We believe that every student at Merlin can and will achieve the goals they desire. We don&#8217;t impose ambition on students, we expect it from them. We expect our students to maintain the same high standards as other students in Texas.&#8217;</p>



<p>A meeting of parents and teachers was held in the school on May 24. Principal Henson told the meeting, Texas has some graduation rules. This is not a dance floor. It is a school graduation ceremony.</p>



<p>Chief Education Officer Nikisha Edward said in a statement, &#8216;Educational institutions have taken various initiatives for underachieving students. For example, various initiatives including more classes per week. Initiatives have also been taken to make students focus more on their studies during their stay in educational institutions. We are also looking at increasing attendance.&#8217;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/most-students-fail-in-texas-usa/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pandya has no regrets about losing to Dhoni</title>
		<link>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/pandya-has-no-regrets-about-losing-to-dhoni/</link>
					<comments>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/pandya-has-no-regrets-about-losing-to-dhoni/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chennai Super Kings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gujarat Titans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hardik Pandya]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mahendra Singh Dhoni]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Two consecutive IPL finals. Had Ravindra Jadeja not done something superhuman in the last two balls, Gujarat would have won two consecutive IPL titles, becoming the first team after Mumbai Indians and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Two consecutive IPL finals. Had Ravindra Jadeja not done something superhuman in the last two balls, Gujarat would have won two consecutive IPL titles, becoming the first team after Mumbai Indians and Chennai Super Kings . Captain Hardik Pandya would have also entered a small list.</p>



<p>After Mahendra Singh Dhoni, Rohit Sharma and Gautam Gambhir, Pandya also won at least two titles as a captain. In the end it didn&#8217;t happen anymore. He lost to Dhoni, whom he admires. Pandya doesn&#8217;t regret losing the final, as the Gujarat captain doesn&#8217;t mind losing to Dhoni.</p>



<p>Gujarat released a video paying tribute to Dhoni before facing Chennai in the first qualifier of the IPL. In that video, Gujarat captain Pandya said about &#8216;Captain Cool&#8217; Dhoni, &#8216;I am a fan of Mahendra Singh Dhoni. You have to be a devil to hate Mahi (Dhoni) .&#8217;</p>



<p>What Pandya said even after the match yesterday, it is clear how much his devotion is towards Dhoni. About Dhoni, the Gujarat captain said, &#8216;I am very happy for Dhoni. It was written in his fate. If I have to lose, I don&#8217;t mind losing to Dhoni. Good things happen to good people.&#8217;</p>



<p>Gujarat skipper Pandya is not making excuses for the loss, saying Chennai played better cricket than Gujarat, saying, &#8216;We win together, we lose together. I am not one to make excuses. Chennai played better cricket than us. The name of Sai Sudarshan must be mentioned. He will do something incredible in the future. I am very happy with the cricketers.&#8217;</p>



<p>Jadeja, who won the final with 10 runs off the last 2 balls, dedicated Chennai&#8217;s title to Dhoni, &#8216;As a team, we want to dedicate this title to Dhoni, a special member of our team.&#8217;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/pandya-has-no-regrets-about-losing-to-dhoni/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://legacy.idrc.ocad.ca/2023/05/30/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
